Imagine you're part of a data science team
假设你是数据科学团队的一员
that's responsible for building a company's recommendation engine.
负责建立公司的推荐引擎
You're sitting at your desk working on a feature
你正坐在办公桌前处理一项功能
that incorporates demographic data like age,
根据年龄、性别和关系状态等
gender, and relationship status to improve recommendations to users.
人口统计数据 改善针对用户的推荐
You're midway through this implementation when
你正做到一半
your boss comes over to notify you that the business intelligence team
老板过来通知你 商业智能团队
predicts that a user's friend groups will produce
预测用户的朋友群组可以在短期内
the best recommendations in the short-term and wanted to prioritize this immediately.
生成最佳推荐 希望你能立即优先完成该功能
Looking at the recommendation engine code you have on your screen,
查看屏幕上的推荐引擎代码
you can see there's a bunch of
可以看到有很多
unfinished non-working code that you've added while working on the demographic feature.
处理人口统计特征时添加的 未完成的代码
Running this code right now would break.
现在运行这些代码会崩溃
If you want to get started on this new friend groups feature now,
如果你想立即开始实现新的朋友群组功能
you'd have to undo all of this work maybe by editing
必须撤消前面这些工作
back lines you've modified and committing out lines of code you added.
或者删除或者注释掉这些未完成的代码
This would be a very messy and risky route,
这会非常混乱和冒险
or say you're using a version control system like Git.
但是 如果你正在使用像 git 这样的版本控制系统
You can simply commit your changes and create another branch for this new feature.
可以直接提交更改 并为此新功能创建另一个分支
Here's what I mean.
详细说明一下
Your company has a Git repository for its recommendation engine and has a master branch,
公司的推荐引擎有一个 git 代码库 其中有一个 master 分支
which holds the code used in production and the develop branch
包含生产中使用的代码 还有一个 develop 分支
which holds the latest stable version of code with changes for the next release.
其中包含最新稳定版本的代码以及下一版本的更改
You have a local version of this repository on your laptop,
你的电脑上有该代码库的本地版本
and to get the latest stable version you pull from the develop branch.
从 develop 分支中获取了最新的稳定版本
When you start working on this demographic feature,
开始处理人口统计功能时
you create a new branch for this called
创建了一个新分支 demographic
"Demographic" and start working on your code in this branch.
然后开始处理此分支中的代码
However, in the middle of your work,
但是做到一半时
you need to work on another feature.
你需要处理另一个功能
So, you commit your changes on
所以你提交 demographic 分支上的更改
this demographic branch and switch back to the develop branch.
切换回 develop 分支
From the stable develop branch,
在稳定的 develop 分支中
you create another branch for a new feature called friend groups.
你为新功能创建另一个分支 friend_group
After you finish your work on the friend groups branch,
完成 friend_group 分支的工作后
you commit your changes,
提交你的更改
switch back to development branch,
切换回 develop 分支
merge it with the friend groups branch,
合并 friend_group 分支
and push this to the remote repository's develop branch.
并将其推送到远程代码库的 develop 分支
Now, you can switch back to
现在你可以切换回
the demographic branch to continue your progress on that feature.
demographic 分支继续你在该功能上的工作
As you can see here,
正如你在这里看到的
proper use of Git commits and branches can help you work
正确使用 git 提交和分支可以帮助你
on multiple features at once and switch between them with ease.
同时处理多个功能 轻松切换